Finding Aid for the Albert McCleery Papers PASC.0098
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Television Projects, 1950-1960; (1-3, 5, 7, 8, 10-20, 22)
  - NBC MATINEE THEATRE
    - Story of Marcia Gordon (The), 6/10/1958 (Box 63)
    - Story of Sarah (The), 9/23/1957 (Box 52)
    - Strong Medicine, 12/28/1956 (Box 40)
    - Strong Medicine (Commercials), 7/10/1957 (Box 49)
    - Sudden Truth (The), 1/8/1957 (Box 40)
    - Suicide Club, 2/25/1958 (Box 58)
    - Summer Cannot Last, 2/15/1956 (Box 26)
    - Sunday in Sonora, 8/2/1957 (Box 50)
    - Sure Thing (The), 12/12/1957 (Box 55)
    - Survival Kit, 1/2/1958 (Box 56)
    - Sylvania and Alcoa (16 items), 1955 (Box 1, Folder 10)
      Schedule for 8/14/55 closed circuit segment, scripts for close circuit segments.
    - Talk You of Killing, 4/4/1957 (Box 44)
    - Taxi to the Moon, 5/31/1956 (Box 31)
    - Technique, 12/20/1955 (Box 24)
    - Tell-Tale Heart (The), 11/6/1956 (Box 38)
    - Temptation for a King, 3/20/1956 (Box 27)
    - Tenth Muse (The), 2/18/1958 (Box 58)
    - Thank You Edmondo, 11/5/1956 (Box 38)
    - There's Always Juliet, 7/2/1956 (Box 33)
    - Therese, 12/3/1956 (Box 39)
    - Things Hoped For, 6/20/1957 (Box 48)
    - Third Person (The), 2/14/1958 (Box 58)
    - Thirteenth Crypt (The), 1/24/1957 (Box 41)
    - This Language Called Love, 1/23/1957 (Box 41)
    - This Man is Dangerous, 2/6/1957 (Box 42)
    - Thread That Runs So True (The), 4/15/1957 (Box 45)
    - Three for the Money, 6/1/1956 (Box 31)
    - Three Kids, 2/4/1957 (Box 41)
    - Three Kids (Commercials), 6/18/1957 (Box 48)
    - Thunderbolt, 1/17/1958 (Box 57)
    - Thursday's Child, 5/9/1957 (Box 46)
    - Time for Action, 8/15/1957 (Box 50)
    - Tin Wedding, 4/24/1956 (Box 29)
    - To Have and to Hold, 5/17/1956 (Box 30)
    - Tone of Time (The), 10/17/1957 (Box 53)
    - Tony Her Son, 3/15/1956 (Box 27)
    - Too Much Johnson, 7/1/1957 (Box 48)
    - Top Platter, 5/6/1958 (Box 62)
    - Touchstone (The), 11/29/1955 (Box 23)
    - Town in a Turmoil, 6/11/1958 (Box 63)
    - Trouble Train (The), 7/3/1957 (Box 48)
    - Two Mrs Carrolls (The), 4/3/1958 (Box 60)
    - Two Picture Deal, 1/8/1958 (Box 56)
    - Uncle Harry, 9/21/1956 (Box 36)
    - Upper Hand (The), 12/11/1956 (Box 39)
    - Valentine's Day, 2/14/1956 (Box 26)
    - Velvet Glove (The), 4/4/1958 (Box 60)
    - Vicarious Years (The), 3/28/1957 (Box 44)
    - Vigilante (The), 3/4/1958 (Box 59)
    - Villa of the Angels, 10/16/1957 (Box 53)
    - Voyage to Mahdok, 2/26/1957 (Box 43)
    - Waiting Swan (The), 9/24/1957 (Box 52)
    - Walk the Sky, 4/11/1958 (Box 60)
    - Washington Square, 6/12/1958 (Box 63)
    - Washington Whispers Murder, 4/18/1958 (Box 61)
    - Ways of Courage (The), 3/25/1957 (Box 44)
    - We Won't Be Any Trouble, 4/2/1957 (Box 44)
    - Wedding in the Family, 3/20/1957 (Box 43)
    - When the Bough Breaks, 2/23/1956 (Box 26)
    - Where Angels Fear to Tread, 8/9/1957 (Box 50)
    - White Headed Boy, 6/12/1957 (Box 48)
    - White Knight (The), 2/8/1956 (Box 25)
    - Whiteoaks, 12/9/1955 (Box 23)
    - Whom Death Has Joined Together, 4/23/1956 (Box 29)
    - Winter in April, 3/27/1956 (Box 28)
    - Winter in April (Commercials), 4/22/1957 (Box 45)
    - With Love We Live, 3/11/1958 (Box 59)
    - Without Fear of Favor, 2/13/1958 (Box 58)
    - Without Sanction, 10/31/1956 (Box 37)
    - Witness to Murder, 11/19/1957 (Box 54)
    - Woman Across the Hall, 10/23/1956 (Box 37)
    - Woman Alone, 9/4/1957 (Box 51)
    - Woman Named Ruby (A), 4/25/1956 (Box 29)
    - Women Have Ways, 8/30/1957 (Box 51)
    - Wuthering Heights, 11/30/1955 (Box 23)
    - Wuthering Heights, 4/8/1957 (Box 45)
    - Yankee Doodler, 8/29/1956 (Box 35)
    - You and I, 3/12/1958 (Box 59)
    - Young and Damned (The), 6/29/1956 (Box 33)
    - Young and Fair (The), 5/23/1958 (Box 62)
    - Young Hands, Young Feet, 4/13/1956 (Box 28)
  - NEW YORK 21, N.Y.
    - Character sketches and background on the series, 1959 (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence dealing mainly with script submissions (9 items), 1959, 1960 (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - Lists of possible series titles, title songs and information on title's legal clearance (12 items), 1959 (Box 15, Folder 9)
    - Pilot script, [1960] (Box 15, Folder 7)
    - Plot synopsis and comments for eight possible episodes (13 items), 1959-1960 (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - Resumes and photographs of actors considered for the role of Mark (Approximately 30 items), 1959 (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - Resumes and photographs of actors considered for the role of Robert (Approximately 40 items), 1959 (Box 15, Folder 3)
      Resumes and photographs of actors considered for the role of Robert. 1959. approx. 40 items
    - Resumes and photographs of actresses considered for the role of Louise (22 items), 1959 (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - Resumes, photos and letters of application for roles in the series (approximately 30 items), 1959 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - WARRANT FOR ARREST
    - Dead Center (12 items), 1961 (Box 10, Folder 4)
      Two drafts, script of series opening, lists of actors under consideration, and correspondence
  - YOUR DAY IN COURT
    - kinescope - script written by Emmet Lavery, 1954 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - YOUR PRIZE STORY
    - Between Two Loves, 4/16/1952 (Box 67)
    - Never Say Love, 5/21/1952 (Box 67)
    - Nicest Girl in Town, The, 5/28/1952 (Box 67)
    - Rebound, 5/7/1952 (Box 67)
    - Second Try, 4/13/1952 (Box 67)
    - Something Blue, 4/30/1952 (Box 67)
    - Something New, Something Old, 4/9/1952 (Box 67)
    - Two Loves Have I, 5/14/1952 (Box 67)
- Radio Projects, 1954; (Boxes 10 and 82)
  The series consists of scripts representing Albert McCleery's work as radio producer and director for the program, Inheritance.
  - INHERITANCE, 1954 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - INHERITANCE, 1954 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - INHERITANCE, 1954 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - INHERITANCE, 4/4/1954 (Box 82)
  - INHERITANCE, 4/11/1954 (Box 82)
  - INHERITANCE, 4/18/1954 (Box 82)
  - INHERITANCE, 4/25/1954 (Box 82)
  - INHERITANCE, 5/2/1954 (Box 82)
  - INHERITANCE, 5/9/1954 (Box 82)
  - INHERITANCE, 5/16/1954 (Box 82)
  - INHERITANCE, 5/23/1954 (Box 82)
  - INHERITANCE, 5/30/1954 (Box 82)
  - INHERITANCE, 6/6/1954 (Box 82)
  - INHERITANCE, 6/20/1954 (Box 82)
  - INHERITANCE, 7/4/1954 (Box 82)
  - INHERITANCE, 7/18/1954 (Box 82)
  - INHERITANCE, 8/1/1954 (Box 82)
  - INHERITANCE, 8/15/1954 (Box 82)
  - INHERITANCE, 8/28/1954 (Box 82)
  - INHERITANCE, 9/4/1954 (Box 82)
  - INHERITANCE, 9/19/1954 (Box 82)
- UNPRODUCED PROJECTS, (Boxes 1948-1954, 1957, 1960)
  The series consists of files pertaining to unproduced projects created by and submitted to McCleery. Includes script material and occasional of budget information. The series is arranged alphabetically by projects created by McCleery and projects submitted to McCleery.
  - CREATED BY MCCLEERY
    - Four program proposals and a package presentation agreement (7 items), 1958, 1961 (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - List and synopsis of properties gathered as possibilites for SUSPENSE SHOW (7 items), 1959 (Box 19, Folder 6)
    - McCleery projects inventory (1 item), no date (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - ALEXANDER THE GREAT revised script with addenda for (1 item), 1963 (Box 17, Folder 9)
      Possibly for HALLMARK [?].
    - CARAVAN SHOW budget and Gringo proposal (2 items), 1962 (Box 9, Folder 10)
    - CHAPLAIN AND THE COMMANDER (THE) script(1 item), 1961 (Box 17, Folder 8)
      Prepared for the Army Pictorial Center
    - CRIME CLUB budget estimate; ELLERY QUEEN actual budget and GATHERING OF THE CLANS proposal (3 items), 1958, 1961 (Box 9, Folder 12)
    - DOCTOR NEXT DOOR (The) - budget and ideas (15 items), 1954 (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Ford Motor Company's THE DARK DARK NIGHT proposal and story ideas (30 minute and 60 minute versions) (2 items), no date (Box 9, Folder 14)
    - GRANDMA IS A SHERIFF, A WHEELS, and MURDER IN THE FIRST PERSON program proposals (3 items), no date (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - GREAT HOURS (The) (formerly known as TV's Great Hours - budget and proposal (3 items), 1962 (Box 16, Folder 13)
    - IT PAYS TO READ script drafts, budgets and proposals (television game show) (17 items), 1962 (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - MALTESE FALCON (THE) program proposal; NBC CAROUSEL THEATER program proposals; and The Cage treatment for (3 items), [1958?], 1965 (Box 9, Folder 15)
    - MANHATTAN REPORT proposal; materials for PROJECT II (2 items), 1961, 1962 (Box 9, Folder 9)
      Original folder labeled by McCleery as Mute Pigs.
    - MIDNIGHT MYSTERY proposal for (1 item), no date (Box 17, Folder 12)
    - PACIFIC OCEAN PLAYHOUSE proposal for (1 item), no date (Box 9, Folder 13)
    - PEER GYNT by Albert McCleery stage adaptation of, no date (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - RALPH EDWARDS THEATRE OF LIFE - budget estimate for proposed schedule (3 items), 1954 (Box 9, Folder 11)
      With budget estimate for Sherwood Shows
    - THAT'S JUST DAISY - scripts and character descriptions, no date (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - THEATRE AMERICANA prospectus and budget (2 items), no date (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - VIEW FROM WITHIN (THE), TALES FROM A FLAT EARTH, and AMERICAN NARRATIVE program proposals (3 items), no date (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - SUBMITTED TO MCCLEERY
    - Correspondence regarding two possible programs: Pearl Lang's PERSEPHONE ASCENDING and Grouch Marx's TIME FOR ELIZABETH (6 items), 1957, 1960 (Box 20, Folder 10)
    - Ideas for productions submited by William Corrington (12 items), 1952 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - Letters noting submissions made by Ashley Buck (4 items), 1953 (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - Radio scripts submitted by Harry W Junkin 1948-1951 (5 items) (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - Synopses and recommendations on suitability for television adaptation of five produced stage plays (5 items), 1960 (Box 17, Folder 7)
    - Television script and treatment submited by Harry W Junkin 1959 (3 items) (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - Treatment and ideas submited by William Robert Yates and two scripts by Guy parent (5 items), 1962 (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - Treatments, one with evocative photographs (19 items), 1958-1961 (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - Untitled treatment (author unknown) (1 item), no date (Box 17, Folder 6)
    - Bitter Wine (Romeo and Juliet in Taos)", by Walt Sheldon script for stage play (1 item), no date (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - Common Sailor (The) - treatment submited by A. J. Palmerio (2 items), 1954 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - DELICATE APE (THE) program and stage play (directed by McCleery) and film adaptation (3 items), no date (Box 17, Folder 11)
    - Eagle Has no Head (The) treatment by Francis Mayers and John Drew Barrymore, no date (Box 16, Folder 8)
    - ECHO - ideas for possible series (1 item), 1960 (Box 16, Folder 7)
    - Everyman script and telecast suggestions submited by Albert Johnson (3 items), 1954 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - INTO THE FIRE by Francis Swann prospectus and The Listener by Allan Sloane treatment (3 items), 1960 (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - JENNY KISSED ME - stage play, shooting script (with timings and camera movements) and cast list (3 items), no date (Box 17, Folder 10)
    - Light and the Dark (The) script submited by Emmet Lavery (12 items), [1950?] (Box 3, Folder 4)
      [Cameo Theatre ?]
    - Lysistrata for President script submited by Maurice Stoller (1 item), no date (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - Morgue (The) and The Road short stories (2 items), no date (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - Night - teaser; and Wonderful Day outline submited by Arch Oboler, including memos 1960 (6 items) (Box 3, Folder 15)
      With memos.
    - Payment in Full by G Donald Waldens script (1 item), 1961 (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - ROGUES GALLERY by William Robert Yeats and SECOND CHANCE by John Haggart proposals, no date (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - Stand by for Murder! script by Arthur Kennard (2 items), no date (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - WATCHERS (THE ) - correspondence and option aggreement for adaptation (4 items), 1959 (Box 19, Folder 5)
      Adaptation of Dolores Hitchins' THE WATCHERS.
- CORRESPONDENCE, 1935-1962; (Boxes 6 and 14)
  The Correspondence Series contains both business and personal correspondence from friends, colleagues and fans.
  - Business and personal correspondence from friends, colleagues and fans 1956 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Business and personal correspondence from friends, colleagues and fans 1960 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Business and personal correspondence from friends, colleagues and fans 1960 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - CBS interoffice communications on a variety of topics (22 items), 1959, 1960 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Letters and cards from friends, colleagues and associates on a variety of topics (Approx. 30 items), 1959 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Letters and cards from friends, colleagues and associates on a variety of topics (Approx. 70 items), 1954 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Letters and cards from friends, colleagues and associates on a variety of topics Approx (20 items), 1953 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Letters and cards from friends, colleagues and associates on a variety of topics (33 items), 1949-1951 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Letters and cards from friends, colleagues and associates on a variety of topics (Approx 20 items), 1955 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Letters and postcards from friends and colleagues on a variety of topics including stock market speculation (7 items), 1952 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Letters from friends, colleagues and associates (Approximately 50 items), 1952 (Box 6, Folder 2)
    With McCleery's essay: Five 'Do's and Dont's' For Television Production.
  - Letters from friends, colleagues and associates on a variety of topics Approx (10 items), 1962 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Letters from friends, colleagues and associates on a variety of topics (Approx 20 items), 1961 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Letters from friends, colleagues and associates on a variety of topics (Approx. 70 items), 1953 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Letters from friends, lawyers, special interest groups and job applicants (22 items), 1935-1948 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Letters of application from people seeking positions in television (6 items), 1953 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - NBC interoffice communication on a variety of topics (10 items), 1955, 1956 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Radio and Television Directors Guild letter (1 item), 1957 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Business and personal correspondence from friends, colleagues and fans 1956 (Box 14, Folder 1)
- PROFESSIONAL SUBJECT FILES, 1950s-1960; (Boxes 11, 12, 20, 21)
  The bulk of the series consists of resumes, letters of application, and photographs from actors, directors, and production staff. Aslo includes a small amount of clippings on video technologies, a small number of items pertaining to the Academy of Television Arts and Sciences, AFTRA and the Directors Guild.
  - ACADEMY OF TELEVISION ARTS AND SCIENCES (24 items), 1960-1963 (Box 12, Folder 3)
    Correspondence, minutes, and constituiton of the Academy.
  - AMERICAN FEDERATION OF TELEVISION AND RADIO ARTISTS (8 items), 1954, 1960 (Box 12, Folder 1)
    AFTRA negotiation reports and Codes of Fair practice for Network Television and Commercial Radio; official correspondence from American Federation of Musicians.
  - CBS Television Workshop - Writer's Seminar, 1960 (Box 11, Folder 6)
    Two lists of CBS writers, one, with addresses
  - Clippings, 1971 (Box 20, Folder 5)
    Articles collected by McCleery on CATV, videotape, and other video technologies. 28 items.
  - DIRECTORS' GUILDS (46 items), 1955-1961 (Box 12, Folder 2)
    Constitution, by-laws and correspondence from Directors Guild of America, Radio and Television Directors Guild, and Screen Directors Guild. 1955-1961. 46 items.
  - Director's resumes and letters of application (11 items), 1956, 1960 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - FILM ESTIMATES (7 items), 1953 (Box 20, Folder 1)
    Correspondence dealing with McCleery's intention to work on a television film series. 1953. 7 items.
  - List of designers and their credits and a letter of application (2 items), 1959 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - PRODUCER'S Biographies (3 items), 1959 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - PRODUCTION STAFF resumes (24 items), 1959, 1960 (Box 11, Folder 10)
    Resumes and letters of application for positions in television production.
  - PRODUCTION STAFF resumes (45 items), 1955, 1956 (Box 11, Folder 9)
    Resumes and letters of application for positions in television production selected for further consideration. 1955, 1956. 45 items.
  - Resumes (37 items), 1955-1956, 1959-1960 (Box 11, Folder 3)
    Resumes and letters of application from actors, directors, and agents, lists of available actors.
  - Resumes and Photographs, 1950's (Box 11, Folder 1)
    Resumes, photographs, and letters of application.
  - Resumes and Photographs, 1950's (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Resumes and photographs - B, 1960 (Box 21, Folder 1)
    Resumes, letters of application, and photographs from actors seeking roles (last names beginning with the letter B.
  - Resumes and photographs - C, 1960 (Box 21, Folder 2)
    Resumes, letters of application, and photographs from actors seeking roles (last names beginning with the letter C.
  - Resumes and photographs - D, 1960 (Box 21, Folder 3)
    Resumes, letters of application, and photographs from actors seeking roles (last names beginning with the letter D.
  - Resumes and photographs - E, 1960 (Box 21, Folder 4)
    Resumes, letters of application, and photographs from actors seeking roles (last names beginning with the letter E.
  - Resumes and photographs - F, 1960 (Box 21, Folder 5)
    Resumes, letters of application, and photographs from actors seeking roles (last names beginning with the letter F.
  - Resumes and photographs - G, 1960 (Box 21, Folder 6)
    Resumes, letters of application, and photographs from actors seeking roles (last names beginning with the letter G.
  - Resumes and photographs - H, 1960 (Box 21, Folder 7)
    Resumes, letters of application, and photographs from actors seeking roles (last names beginning with the letter H.
  - Resumes and photographs - I, 1960 (Box 21, Folder 18)
    Resumes, letters of application, and photographs from actors seeking roles (last names beginning with the letter I).
  - Resumes and photographs - J, 1960 (Box 21, Folder 8)
    Resumes, letters of application, and photographs from actors seeking roles (last names beginning with the letter J).
  - Resumes and Photographs - K, 1960 (Box 21, Folder 9)
    Resumes, letters of application, and photographs from actors seeking roles (last names beginning with K.
  - Resumes and photographs - L, 1960 (Box 21, Folder 10)
    Resumes, letters of application, and photographs from actors seeking roles (last names beginning with the letter L).
  - Resumes and photographs - Mc, 1960 (Box 21, Folder 12)
    Resumes, letters of application, and photographs from actors seeking roles (last names beginning with the letters Mc).
  - Resumes and photographs - M, 1960 (Box 21, Folder 11)
    Resumes, letters of application, and photographs from actors seeking roles (last names beginning with the letter M.
  - Resumes and photographs - N, 1960 (Box 21, Folder 13)
    Resumes, letters of application, and photographs from actors seeking roles (last names beginning with the letter N).
  - Resumes and photographs - O, 1960 (Box 21, Folder 14)
    Resumes, letters of application, and photographs from actors seeking roles (last names beginning with the letter O).
  - Resumes and photographs - P, 1960 (Box 21, Folder 15)
    Resumes, letters of application, and photographs from actors seeking roles (last names beginning with the letter P).
  - Resumes and photographs - R, 1960 (Box 21, Folder 16)
    Resumes, letters of application, and photographs from actors seeking roles (last names beginning with the letter R.
  - Resumes and photographs - S, 1960 (Box 21, Folder 17)
    Resumes, letters of application, and photographs from actors seeking roles (last names beginning with the letter S).
  - Resumes and photographs - W, 1960 (Box 21, Folder 20)
    Resumes, letters of application, and photographs from actors seeking roles (last names beginning with W.
  - Resumes and photographs - V, 1960 (Box 21, Folder 19)
    Resumes, letters of application, and photographs from actors seeking roles (last names beginning with the letter V.
  - Resumes and photographs - X, Y, Z, 1960 (Box 21, Folder 21)
    Resumes, letters of application, and photographs from actors seeking roles (last names beginning with the letters X, Y, and Z).
  - Television Producers Guild (4 items), 1959, 1962 (Box 12, Folder 4)
    Correspondence from Television Producers Guild, and information on Independent Producers' Corporation. 1959, 1962. 4 items.
- NETWORK FILES
  Network Files are a small number of files pertaining to CBS and NBC. Among the files are publicity releases, inter-departmental communications, broad policy information, synopses, and a transcript of a Harry Reasoner interview for Vote for Me, among other network-related documents. The series is arranged alphabetically by file titles.
  - CBS Eastern Story Department synopsis (28 items), 1961 (Box 20, Folder 8)
    Published materials under consideration for television adaptation.
  - CBS expense reports and receipts for work requests, travel and hotels (9 items), 1960, 1961 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - CBS NEWS - VOTE FOR ME (4 items), 1961 (Box 14, Folder 12)
    Transcript and review of VOTE FOR ME: Harry Reasoner's interview with nine minor candidates in the New Jersey governor's election. 1961. 4 items.
  - CBS office communications on decisions and policy matters (15 items), 1959 (Box 12, Folder 5)
    Office communications on decisions and policy matters. 1959. 15 items.
  - CBS Program Department Personnel lists and list of members of the CBS 20- Year Club (2 items), 1958, 1961 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - CBS Program Schedule presenation by Frank Stanton (CBS President) (3 items), 1959-1960 (Box 14, Folder 10)
    Presentation before the F.C.C.: Statement, Classification of CBS Program Schedule, date and content list of CBS' 1959 season.
  - CBS PUBLICITY RELEASES, 1961 (Box 11, Folder 11)
    Advance program schedules, schedule corrections, and releases on programs and actors.
  - CBS PUBLICITY RELEASES, 1961 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - NBC Interdepartment mail on hirings, color commercials, special effects (15 items), 1953-1955 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - NBC lists of personnel names and addresses (9 items), 1953, 1954 (Box 14, Folder 8)
    Technical operations, engineering, executives, Hallmark personnell, and various Christmas card lists. 1953, 1954. 9 items.
  - NBC Policy concerning submission of ideas and other materials (1 item), 1954 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - NBC production facilites and services rate manual #3 with letter on matter (1 item), 1954 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - NBC Radio and Television Broadcast Standards and Network Production Facilities and Standards, 1956 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - NETWORK PROGRAM COSTS, 1962 (Box 20, Folder 7)
    Estimated weekly network TV program costs for ABC, CBS, and NBC; clipping from VARIETY. 1962. 1 item.
- THEATER FILES, Eary 1940s, 1950s and 1960s; (Boxes 4, 7, 14, 16, and 18)
  The Theater Files include materials documenting McCleery's affiliation with the Pasadena Playhouse, Stage Magazine, Threshold Theatre, and educational theater. The series is arranged alphabetically by file titles.
  - Correspondence and programs re. educational theater (22 items), 1951-1953, 1959 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    With National Theatre Conference code, regulations, and objectives.
  - Institute for Advanced Studies in the Theatre Arts - correspondence (3 items), 1960 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Letters and article by McCleery from his work at STAGE magazine (14 items), 1940-1941 (Box 14, Folder 13)
    Mostly concerning the Confederacy of American Community Theatres.